# SEAN GRINDAL

COMSCI STUDENT & FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

HTTPS://SEANGRINDAL.DEV

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Enthusiastic frontend developer and student. Started working professionally as a contract frontend developer at the beginning of highschool. Experienced leading multiple development project, and architecting internal development tools. I love to work closely with executives to bring about company visions and goals.

# CONTACT

- hello@seangrindal.dev
- seangrindal.dev
- LinkedIn
- <u>Github</u>

# LANGUAGES / SKILLS

- JS/ES6 (4/y)
- HTML/PUG (4/y)
- CSS/SCSS(4/y)
- Vue.js (3/y)
- Nuxt.js (2/y)
- Node.js (4/y)
- Wordpress (3/y)
- PHP (3/y)
- Python (1/y)
- Git (4/y)
- Notion (2/y)
- Organization and writing of company tech documentation
- Conducting frontend interviews
- Planning frontend web projects
- Architecting internal codebases and templates for code reusability

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# **Part-Time Consultant Developer**

ANOA (Sept 2021 - Present)

- Responsible for planning and overseeing the development of ongoing client projects
- Continued onboarding of a new developer
- Maintenance of important codebases and documentation

#### **Lead Developer**

ANOA (Aug 2020 - Aug 2021)

- Lead planning and development of various internal codebases, patterns, and templates used across client websites
- Architected a new headless CMS and frontend schema to be used across all client portfolio projects
- Responsible for an internal demos website to facilitate the design of client projects
- Vetted resumes and interviewed new potential developers
- Worked closely with the CEO on road mapping and company vision

# **Part-Time Contract Frontend Developer**

Motiv (2018 - Present)

- Working closely with designers to program the frontend of various client websites using ES6, HTML, SCSS, Vue, Node.js
- Working with a team of other developers on larger web projects, to plan and develop web components
- Helped plan and development internal development patterns

#### **PROJECTS**

### **Custom Cursor JS**

- https://custom-cursor-js.netlify.app/

#### **3D Equation Modeller**

- https://seangrindal.dev/experiments/3d-equation-modeller/

#### View professional projects on my website

- https://seangrindal.dev

# **EDUCATION**

# **University of Toronto**

#### Computer Science '25

- 1st year, currently have a 4.0 GPA
- Discrete mathematics and proofs
- Analyzing running time and algorithm complexity